const computerQuestions = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "What does the 'C' in CPU stand for?",
    options: ["Cat", "Central", "Cup", "Candy"],
    correctOption: "Central",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which device is used to type on a computer?",
    options: ["Mouse", "Keyboard", "Screen", "Printer"],
    correctOption: "Keyboard",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What color is usually used for a stop button on a computer?",
    options: ["Red", "Green", "Blue", "Yellow"],
    correctOption: "Red",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What do we use to click on things on a computer screen?",
    options: ["Mouse", "Keyboard", "Camera", "Speaker"],
    correctOption: "Mouse",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which of these is a computer part?",
    options: ["Tree", "Monitor", "Ball", "Car"],
    correctOption: "Monitor",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which device shows pictures and videos on a computer?",
    options: ["Monitor", "Mouse", "Keyboard", "Speaker"],
    correctOption: "Monitor",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What does a printer do?",
    options: [
      "Prints pictures and words",
      "Plays music",
      "Shows videos",
      "Types letters",
    ],
    correctOption: "Prints pictures and words",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which of these is a computer?",
    options: ["Laptop", "Television", "Microwave", "Phone"],
    correctOption: "Laptop",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What do you press to turn on a computer?",
    options: ["Power button", "Enter key", "Mouse", "Monitor"],
    correctOption: "Power button",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the name of the big box in a desktop computer?",
    options: ["CPU", "Mouse", "Printer", "Screen"],
    correctOption: "CPU",
  },
];

export default computerQuestions;
